

SAMUEL GARCIA LABRA

Software Developer

CONTACT

polilabra@gmail.com 🖂

+52 5521889209 🖉

Mexico City ©

Website $\stackrel{\circ}{\sim}$

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Eng. Communications & Electronics

IPN ESIME ZACATENCO 2017 - 2024

SKILLS

Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
Python, PHP, C++, SQL
Flutter
Git, GitHub
VS Code, IntelliJ, Eclipse
Chrome Dev Tools
Figma
UX / UI

APTITUDES

Enjoy working as a team Flexible Innovative Analytic Self taught

PROFILE

Communications & electronics engineer specialized in software development.

My goal is to become a proficient software developer. I've used different programming languages with best coding practices, and understand the SDLC. I take courses online and in person about tech and design.

EXPERIENCE

Developer

November 2024 - Current

Training about software development topics such as:

- · Object Oriented Programming with Java
- Version Control of code using Git
- Use of IDE for development and debugging
- Perform API requests using Postman

Developer

NTT DATA

INDRA

June 2024 – September 2024

Took frontend related courses, and learned things like:

- Programming Web components with JavaScript
- Use of good coding practices
- Software construction stages
- SCRUM foundations certificate

LANGUAGES

Advanced English Native Spanish